[{"answer": "That's what's said happened and that's what's going around, that the kids made or were attempting to make a run or to escape.", "docId": "121219pmt", "aSentId": 44, "question": "But did it surprise you that in that moment, even at his young age, that he was showing such enterprising courage?", "qSentId": 43}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, this is not as rare as people might think.", "docId": "121219pmt", "aSentId": 88, "question": "What is the answer?", "qSentId": 87}, {"answer": "I think the president recognized today in a very appropriate statement that we have to take a look at a variety of risk factors that have created this epidemic, this carnage.", "docId": "121219pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "And is the president right to identify the solution to at least trying to deal with this as being the -- banning these type of assault weapons and the high-capacity magazine clips and also, as Mayor Booker says here, trying to register the ownership of guns in a more sensible manner?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "My reaction is I -- first off, on behalf of the entire Michigan Coalition for Responsible Gun Owners, I want to express sincere sympathy to those who have lost loved ones.", "docId": "121219pmt", "aSentId": 187, "question": "What is your reaction?", "qSentId": 186}, {"answer": "Well, my thinking on this is they are out there.", "docId": "121219pmt", "aSentId": 202, "question": "As Christiane says, these belong -- not belong but they are found on the battlefields of Sarajevo, of Syria?", "qSentId": 201}, {"answer": "After Dunblane, they put in these bans.", "docId": "121219pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "OK, and what happened after '97 to the murder rate in England?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "Piers, this is what's going to change it.", "docId": "121219pmt", "aSentId": 324, "question": "What is going to change this culture?", "qSentId": 323}, {"answer": "Let me just very quickly say, I'm very sorry to all the parents who lost their children and to the other people who lost the adults in this massacre.", "docId": "121219pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "What is your belief about the claim that many people that, that if the teachers had been armed at Sandy Hook, that they could have averted the disaster, and that civilians should be armed for that reason, to protect themselves from mass killings like this?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "Well, of course.", "docId": "121219pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "But as she said, people should be trained for these use, right?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "Here's what I think: you have to try.", "docId": "121219pmt", "aSentId": 473, "question": "What law do you propose that would have stopped this?", "qSentId": 472}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "121219pmt", "aSentId": 482, "question": "Why don't you tell me, Mr. Lott?", "qSentId": 481}, {"answer": "There's a reason --", "docId": "121219pmt", "aSentId": 491, "question": "How many bullets can it fire in a second?", "qSentId": 490}, {"answer": "The point --", "docId": "121219pmt", "aSentId": 501, "question": "How many bullets does the AR 15 fire a second?", "qSentId": 500}, {"answer": "I'm going to answer your first question.", "docId": "121219pmt", "aSentId": 506, "question": "Do you want to answer or not?", "qSentId": 505}, {"answer": "The point is --", "docId": "121219pmt", "aSentId": 515, "question": "How many bullets does it fire a second?", "qSentId": 514}, {"answer": "You will lose lives.", "docId": "121219pmt", "aSentId": 517, "question": "Can you answer the question or not?", "qSentId": 516}, {"answer": "I think your estimate is high.", "docId": "121219pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "Do you know?", "qSentId": 525}, {"answer": "But I understand your passion, having stood on too many street corners, seen too many bodies, seen the kind of weapons we're pulling of the streets.", "docId": "121219pmt", "aSentId": 550, "question": "If you were trying to debate this in a more rational way than I appear capable of, what would you do?", "qSentId": 549}, {"answer": "There are three points that I think need to be raised.", "docId": "121219pmt", "aSentId": 581, "question": "What do you think of this debate?", "qSentId": 580}, {"answer": "You know, I think getting rid of the assault weapons, you know, it is not a perfect bill, but we will never be able to legislate against evil.", "docId": "121219pmt", "aSentId": 590, "question": "Do you want to see these assault rifles just gone?", "qSentId": 589}, {"answer": "I am.", "docId": "121219pmt", "aSentId": 613, "question": "Are you aghast that it isn't a national thing?", "qSentId": 612}, {"answer": "I absolutely believe in banning those weapons.", "docId": "121219pmt", "aSentId": 629, "question": "What is your view?", "qSentId": 628}, {"answer": "My view is that all military style weapons should be banned, period, and Background checks for all.", "docId": "121219pmt", "aSentId": 640, "question": "What is your view?", "qSentId": 639}]